obermatt.com 2013-12-02

# Obermatt: Privacy

**Introduction**

This privacy statement applies to Obermatt AG which controls and makes use of visitor information collected via this site. If you as a visitor choose to register or submit information to this Website, you agree to the use of such data in accordance with this privacy statement. 

Please note that this site contains links to other sites. Obermatt AG has no responsibility for these third-party Web sites, which are governed by the Terms of Use and privacy policies, if any, of the applicable third-party content providers. 

**Information Collection**

As a visitor, you do not have to submit any personal information in order to use the Web site.  The site collects only personally identifiable information that is specifically and voluntarily provided by visitors.  Such information may consist of, but is not limited to, your name, current job title, company address, email address and telephone and fax numbers. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

To ensure that our Web site is well managed and to facilitate improved navigation within the site, we or our service provider(s) may use cookies (small text files stored in a users browser) or Web beacons (electronic images that allow the Web site to count visitors who have accessed a particular page and to access certain cookies) to collect aggregate data. We may use such devices to track information on our systems and identify categories of visitors by items such as IP address, domain, browser type and pages visited. 

This information is used to analyze the number of visitors to different areas of the site and to make sure that our Web site continues to serve as a useful, effective information source. 

Neither cookies nor Web beacons collect personal information such as your name or email address. Further, most browsers permit individuals to decline cookies. 

**Information Use**

Personal information is used only for limited purposes.  We may use the information you submit to create a personal profile to customize our response to further requests or inquiries.  We will ensure that our marketing activities comply with applicable law, and implement procedures to obtain necessary consents before sending you email containing information about Obermatt AG service offerings. 

You may at any time request that we discontinue sending you such materials.  

**Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**

Although we may provide visitors information to service providers that handle information on our behalf, we will usually not share the information with third parties. 

**Data Security**

We have in place reasonable commercial standards of technology and operational security to protect all information provided by visitors from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

Obermatt AG reserves the right to modify or amend this privacy statement at any time and for any reason. Nothing contained herein creates or is intended to create a contract or agreement between Obermatt AG and any user visiting the Web site or providing identifying information of any kind.
